You've seen the story through the eyes of the law... Now see
it through the eyes of The Manson Family.
The Manson Family is a crime, drama, history film directed by Jim Van Bebber.
A dramatization of the horrific and notorious Manson Family
Murders, in the form of super 8 home movies.
Charlie Manson, played by Marcelo Games.
Tex Watson, played by Marc Pitman.
Bobby, played by Jim Van Bebber.
Leslie van Houten, played by Amy Yates.
Patty Krenwinkel, played by Leslie Orr.
Sadie Atkins, played by Maureen Allisse.
The Manson Family is a 1997 American true crime exploitation horror film
written, produced, edited, and  directed by Jim Van Bebber.
The film covers the lives of Charles Manson and his family of followers.
The tone is emotional.